Question(q1):
 question: "Which city is the capital of the Indian state of Karnataka?|Bangalore|Mumbai|New Delhi|Chennai"
 answer: "Bangalore"

Question(q2):
 question: "The only American president elected to more than two terms?|Abraham Lincoln|George Washinton|James Monroe|Thomas Jefferson"
 answer: "Franklin D. Roosevelt"

Question(q3):
 question: "Who conducted the first ever Hackathon event?|Sun Micro Systems|Microsoft|OpenBSD|Apache"
 answer: "OpenBSD"

Question(q4):
 question: "Which city is the capital of New York state?|New York City|Albany|Utica|Binghamton"
 answer: "Albany"
 
Question(q5):
 question: "What is the height of Statue of Liberty?|56 meters|70 meters|46 meters|112 meters"
 answer: "46 meters"
 
Question(q6):
 question: "What was Times Square known as before named what it is now?|York Square|Kamakshi Palya|Longacre Square|Bloomingdale Square"
 answer: "Longacre Square"

Question(q7):
 question: "What was Times Square known as before named what it is now?|York Square|Kamakshi Palya|Longacre Square|Bloomingdale Square"
 answer: "Longacre Square"

Question(q8):
 question: "What were the New York Knicks' official name in their first ever season?|Knicks|Knickerbockers|BockerKnickers|Bockers"
 answer: "Knickerbockers"

Question(q9):
 question: "Which is the highest grossing film franchise?|Star Wars|James Bond|Lord of the Rings|Harry Potter"
 answer: "Harry Potter"

Question(q10):
 question: "Who is the highest grossing film actor of all-time?|Tom Cruise|Brad Bitt|Leonardo Di Caprio|Samuel L Jackson"
 answer: "Samuel L Jackson"
